{
    "subject": "resource/Samuel_Karlin",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Illinois_Institute_of_Technology",
    "human_readable": "Samuel Karlin attended Illinois Institute of Technology.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9879270195960999,
            "question": "Is Samuel Karlin associated with Illinois Institute of Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9869592785835266,
            "question": "What might Samuel Karlin have studied at Illinois Institute of Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9370274543762207,
            "question": "Name a person who attended Illinois Institute of Technology."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9097718000411987,
            "question": "Who attended Illinois Institute of Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8936470746994019,
            "question": "What institution did Samuel Karlin attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.810936450958252,
            "question": "Where did Samuel Karlin attend school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7742540836334229,
            "question": "What is the name of the school Samuel Karlin attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6240752339363098,
            "question": "What type of school is Illinois Institute of Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5795784592628479,
            "question": "Samuel Karlin is connected to which university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5314610004425049,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Samuel Karlin's education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Samuel Karlin attended Illinois Institute of Technology.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7751_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Samuel Karlin is connected to which university?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7751_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of school is Illinois Institute of Technology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7751_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the school Samuel Karlin attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7751_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7751_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. All five documents mention that Samuel Karlin attended the Illinois Institute of Technology, and two of them (64.txt and 84.txt) specifically state that he received a bachelor's degree in mathematics from there in 1944."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in multiple documents, which indicate that Samuel Karlin received his bachelor\u2019s degree in mathematics from the Illinois Institute of Technology."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}